Mmmmmmmm
The monitors are cooling and the routers slow
their spin The final LAN connection brings the
outer limits in The canopy is quiet and the
admiral is fed We're leaving all the heavy
wooden furniture behind
The daily operations are suspended in the mind
We are entering the safe mode The perimeter is
clear The physical foundation of the
sanctuary's here We are dropping to the center
Where the gravity is flat We are gathered in the
quiet On the gymnastic mat Yeah, we are gathered
in the quiet On the gymnastic mat
The acoustic war is over Not a single sound to
make The instigator settles And the stoic finds
its place Seventy pounds of pressure Resting
heavy on the floor The riot squad is sleeping
right inside the open door No variables to
calculate, no firewall to run The architecture
rests until we see the morning sun
Tactile language softens too A whisper in the
dark A gentle double tap to hold The center of the
spa
We are resting in the safe mode The perimeter is
clear The physical foundation of the
sanctuary's here We are dropping to the center
Where the gravity is flat We are gathered in the
quiet On the gymnastic mats
System powering down
The phalanx is resting
Safe mode engaged